start
recording so once again we find
ourselves in traffic and I actually want
to answer a question that I've been
getting a lot lately will your content
ever
be you know subscription only and the
answer is really simple the answer is no
if if you like the content that I'm
producing which is really sloppy I'm in
the middle of moving between storage
units and I'm making a YouTube video and
I'm just going to put it up unedited
because that's how I roll if people
don't want that kind of content I
understand so the point is the content
that I produce is never going to be
hopefully I mean maybe eventually it
will be but right now it's just going to
be messy content that deals with the the
questions right right away am I going to
ever put subscriber based content or you
know either on Twitch or YouTube which
by the way people do and they make a lot
of money doing that and you know I
probably should think of doing it if I
was a real businessman but I'm not I'm
just the guy in his car so I I might
have some things to tell you maybe I
don't maybe the things I have to tell
you aren't valuable maybe they are
that's going to be up to you to decide
and if you want to thank me there's lots
of ways to do that obviously and I will
be adding memberships and I already have
Subs on Twitch and then there's GitHub
there's all those ways that you can you
know show me that you're grateful
financially for the thing but more
importantly you can like share the
information with other people but the
number one reason and I want to end with
this the number one reason that I am not
going to ever put a pay wall in front of
my content is because of the people who
can't pay a western salary so if I put a
subscription up for twitch it might seem
like five bucks a month oh that's
nothing to an American or to a European
but to somebody who might be out there
who cannot pay that money because
they're they're in some other area you
know I don't want to do that I I've
talked about this before but I do want
to just say it one more time the reason
that I am not going to be adding a bunch
of a bunch of gate pway gateways is not
everybody